{
    "subject": "resource/James_Tien_(politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/party",
    "object": "resource/Liberal_Party_(Hong_Kong)",
    "human_readable": "James Tien is a member of the Liberal Party (Hong Kong).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9795881509780884,
            "question": "Is James Tien a member of a political party in Hong Kong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8735183477401733,
            "question": "What political party is James Tien a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8587111234664917,
            "question": "In Hong Kong, what political affiliation does James Tien hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8082926273345947,
            "question": "What is the name of James Tien's political party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7985360026359558,
            "question": "Who is James Tien?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7548339366912842,
            "question": "Which political group does James Tien belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7510451078414917,
            "question": "What is the name of the political party James Tien is associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7220895290374756,
            "question": "Is James Tien involved in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6928324103355408,
            "question": "What is the political stance of James Tien?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6151917576789856,
            "question": "To which country's political system does James Tien belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Tien is a member of the Liberal Party (Hong Kong).",
            "html": "dbpedia_7888_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the political stance of James Tien?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7888_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is James Tien involved in politics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7888_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the political party James Tien is associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7888_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7888_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that James Tien is the honorary chairman of Hong Kong's pro-Beijing Liberal Party, and a former member of the city's legislative council."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports James Tien's association with the Liberal Party in Hong Kong. For instance, document 26 mentions \"Mr James Tien is a senior member of the city's pro-business Liberal Party,\" which directly supports the statement that James Tien is a member of the Liberal Party (Hong Kong)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}